{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031297814","data":{"timestamp":" 947031297813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" fefb63dd-c043-4108-9d9c-70e76be9b0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-de-be"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031314728","data":{"timestamp":" 947031314728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" fefb63dd-c043-4108-9d9c-70e76be9b0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_mdo-mjo-ha"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031319791","data":{"timestamp":" 947031319791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" fefb63dd-c043-4108-9d9c-70e76be9b0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_mo-ha-ndi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031324782","data":{"timestamp":" 947031324782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" fefb63dd-c043-4108-9d9c-70e76be9b0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_mpa-ha-mta"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031329494","data":{"timestamp":" 947031329493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" fefb63dd-c043-4108-9d9c-70e76be9b0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_mli-ha-thi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031333918","data":{"timestamp":" 947031333917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" fefb63dd-c043-4108-9d9c-70e76be9b0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_twa-ha-no"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031338364","data":{"timestamp":" 947031338364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" fefb63dd-c043-4108-9d9c-70e76be9b0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-chi-nge"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031343028","data":{"timestamp":" 947031343028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" fefb63dd-c043-4108-9d9c-70e76be9b0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_nye-ha-pi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031347810","data":{"timestamp":" 947031347810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" fefb63dd-c043-4108-9d9c-70e76be9b0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_mfu-twe-ha"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031352795","data":{"timestamp":" 947031352795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" fefb63dd-c043-4108-9d9c-70e76be9b0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_do-mfa-ha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031358583","data":{"timestamp":" 947031358583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" fefb63dd-c043-4108-9d9c-70e76be9b0af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_do-mfa-ha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031389298","data":{"timestamp":" 947031389298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 0f8822a8-03db-4029-87d1-dafce6c1a990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mta_ha_mzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031395940","data":{"timestamp":" 947031395940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 0f8822a8-03db-4029-87d1-dafce6c1a990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_mlu_mka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031402568","data":{"timestamp":" 947031402568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 0f8822a8-03db-4029-87d1-dafce6c1a990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ya_ha_chu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031409230","data":{"timestamp":" 947031409229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 0f8822a8-03db-4029-87d1-dafce6c1a990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ku_ha_mno"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031415886","data":{"timestamp":" 947031415886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 0f8822a8-03db-4029-87d1-dafce6c1a990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_mzu_bwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031422569","data":{"timestamp":" 947031422568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 0f8822a8-03db-4029-87d1-dafce6c1a990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nju_mke_ha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031429196","data":{"timestamp":" 947031429196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 0f8822a8-03db-4029-87d1-dafce6c1a990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mpa_ha_mwo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031435829","data":{"timestamp":" 947031435829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 0f8822a8-03db-4029-87d1-dafce6c1a990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ki_ha_mmo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031442440","data":{"timestamp":" 947031442440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 0f8822a8-03db-4029-87d1-dafce6c1a990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mbe_ha_twi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031449060","data":{"timestamp":" 947031449059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 0f8822a8-03db-4029-87d1-dafce6c1a990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_nyi_we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031461110","data":{"timestamp":" 947031461110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 0f8822a8-03db-4029-87d1-dafce6c1a990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_ha_nyi_we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031485160","data":{"timestamp":" 947031485159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HA"," userResponse":" HA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031487298","data":{"timestamp":" 947031487298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HA"," userResponse":" HA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031488900","data":{"timestamp":" 947031488900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" he"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HE"," userResponse":" HE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031491660","data":{"timestamp":" 947031491660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" he"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HE"," userResponse":" HE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031493260","data":{"timestamp":" 947031493259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HI"," userResponse":" HI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031498652","data":{"timestamp":" 947031498652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031500226","data":{"timestamp":" 947031500226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HO"," userResponse":" HO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031504620","data":{"timestamp":" 947031504620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031506228","data":{"timestamp":" 947031506227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HU"," userResponse":" HU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031508818","data":{"timestamp":" 947031508817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HU"," userResponse":" HU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031510846","data":{"timestamp":" 947031510844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" hu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031510993","data":{"timestamp":" 947031510993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 25a67fd7-9280-4f1a-91a2-940592049ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HU"," userResponse":" HU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031537998","data":{"timestamp":" 947031537997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 4728dc84-0489-4fbf-aa12-072138faac5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HA"," userResponse":" HA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031539057","data":{"timestamp":" 947031539056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 4728dc84-0489-4fbf-aa12-072138faac5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HA"," userResponse":" HA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031539891","data":{"timestamp":" 947031539891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 4728dc84-0489-4fbf-aa12-072138faac5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031539977","data":{"timestamp":" 947031539977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 4728dc84-0489-4fbf-aa12-072138faac5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ha..hu.asc.lc.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HA"," userResponse":" HA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031562633","data":{"timestamp":" 947031562633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 72109143-65a0-4298-a047-0fd363c975dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031567017","data":{"timestamp":" 947031567017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 72109143-65a0-4298-a047-0fd363c975dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031571886","data":{"timestamp":" 947031571886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 72109143-65a0-4298-a047-0fd363c975dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031576406","data":{"timestamp":" 947031576406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 72109143-65a0-4298-a047-0fd363c975dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031580768","data":{"timestamp":" 947031580768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 72109143-65a0-4298-a047-0fd363c975dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031587969","data":{"timestamp":" 947031587969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 72109143-65a0-4298-a047-0fd363c975dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031597828","data":{"timestamp":" 947031597828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 72109143-65a0-4298-a047-0fd363c975dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031605057","data":{"timestamp":" 947031605057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 72109143-65a0-4298-a047-0fd363c975dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031614245","data":{"timestamp":" 947031614245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 72109143-65a0-4298-a047-0fd363c975dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031619551","data":{"timestamp":" 947031619551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 72109143-65a0-4298-a047-0fd363c975dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031625352","data":{"timestamp":" 947031625350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 72109143-65a0-4298-a047-0fd363c975dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031640644","data":{"timestamp":" 947031640644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031641028","data":{"timestamp":" 947031641028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031641262","data":{"timestamp":" 947031641262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031641576","data":{"timestamp":" 947031641576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031641810","data":{"timestamp":" 947031641810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031645290","data":{"timestamp":" 947031645288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031645597","data":{"timestamp":" 947031645597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031646523","data":{"timestamp":" 947031646523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031646961","data":{"timestamp":" 947031646961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031649911","data":{"timestamp":" 947031649911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031650202","data":{"timestamp":" 947031650202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031651057","data":{"timestamp":" 947031651056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031651733","data":{"timestamp":" 947031651733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031652481","data":{"timestamp":" 947031652481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031652820","data":{"timestamp":" 947031652819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031653108","data":{"timestamp":" 947031653107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031653436","data":{"timestamp":" 947031653436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031653712","data":{"timestamp":" 947031653712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031657402","data":{"timestamp":" 947031657401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031657797","data":{"timestamp":" 947031657796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031658042","data":{"timestamp":" 947031658041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031658365","data":{"timestamp":" 947031658364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031658611","data":{"timestamp":" 947031658610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031662084","data":{"timestamp":" 947031662083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031662388","data":{"timestamp":" 947031662387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031663303","data":{"timestamp":" 947031663302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031663736","data":{"timestamp":" 947031663736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031666707","data":{"timestamp":" 947031666707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031667000","data":{"timestamp":" 947031667000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031667858","data":{"timestamp":" 947031667857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031668538","data":{"timestamp":" 947031668537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031669286","data":{"timestamp":" 947031669285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031669625","data":{"timestamp":" 947031669624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031669918","data":{"timestamp":" 947031669917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031670244","data":{"timestamp":" 947031670243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031670521","data":{"timestamp":" 947031670521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031673959","data":{"timestamp":" 947031673957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031674065","data":{"timestamp":" 947031674065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3657511e-e860-4d5d-ab12-7b5ce32eb3c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031700961","data":{"timestamp":" 947031700960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 5dd52133-974c-460b-86e4-dcade16a42dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_vi-ja-mpi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031706147","data":{"timestamp":" 947031706147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 5dd52133-974c-460b-86e4-dcade16a42dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_pi-ki-ja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031712391","data":{"timestamp":" 947031712391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 5dd52133-974c-460b-86e4-dcade16a42dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ng'i-ng'e-ja"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031717324","data":{"timestamp":" 947031717324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 5dd52133-974c-460b-86e4-dcade16a42dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_po-nyi-ja"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031724038","data":{"timestamp":" 947031724038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 5dd52133-974c-460b-86e4-dcade16a42dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ja-te-ti"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031729030","data":{"timestamp":" 947031729030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 5dd52133-974c-460b-86e4-dcade16a42dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_we-ja-ng'i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031736657","data":{"timestamp":" 947031736657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 5dd52133-974c-460b-86e4-dcade16a42dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ja-ri-mmo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031748823","data":{"timestamp":" 947031748823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 5dd52133-974c-460b-86e4-dcade16a42dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_mno-ja-ta"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031757745","data":{"timestamp":" 947031757745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 5dd52133-974c-460b-86e4-dcade16a42dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_twa-chu-ja"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031767305","data":{"timestamp":" 947031767305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 5dd52133-974c-460b-86e4-dcade16a42dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ja-mpe-vyu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031773096","data":{"timestamp":" 947031773094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 5dd52133-974c-460b-86e4-dcade16a42dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ja-mpe-vyu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031832778","data":{"timestamp":" 947031832778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ng'a-lu-ja"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031837872","data":{"timestamp":" 947031837872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_mwa-mgu-ja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031842932","data":{"timestamp":" 947031842932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_to-mke-ja"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031850088","data":{"timestamp":" 947031850088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ja-fo-vyi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031857318","data":{"timestamp":" 947031857318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ja-twe-mzu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031864285","data":{"timestamp":" 947031864285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_vi-ja-twe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031869685","data":{"timestamp":" 947031869685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ja-ya-mvu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031874653","data":{"timestamp":" 947031874653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ve-he-ja"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031880324","data":{"timestamp":" 947031880324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ve-he-ja"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031885556","data":{"timestamp":" 947031885556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_mwo-te-ja"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031892038","data":{"timestamp":" 947031892038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_yu-nge-ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031897818","data":{"timestamp":" 947031897817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 3215b593-3cb9-4950-9e68-0fabaf88ea68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_yu-nge-ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031926865","data":{"timestamp":" 947031926865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fa_ja_na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031933519","data":{"timestamp":" 947031933518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ze_du_ja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031941131","data":{"timestamp":" 947031941130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ze_du_ja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031947796","data":{"timestamp":" 947031947795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_du_wi_ja"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031954459","data":{"timestamp":" 947031954459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_cho_ja_gi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031961131","data":{"timestamp":" 947031961130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ja_ngu_ju"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031967781","data":{"timestamp":" 947031967781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vi_ja_mlu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031974462","data":{"timestamp":" 947031974461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_we_ja_sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031981119","data":{"timestamp":" 947031981119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_msta_ja_mji"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031987774","data":{"timestamp":" 947031987774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ja_cha_ndo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031994425","data":{"timestamp":" 947031994425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ja_mje_ru"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032002303","data":{"timestamp":" 947032002302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 6b32fcfd-576b-424e-8f7f-0d9d115a8431"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ja..ja.noShow..8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_ja_mje_ru"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032025735","data":{"timestamp":" 947032025734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032026800","data":{"timestamp":" 947032026795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JA"," userResponse":" JA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032030125","data":{"timestamp":" 947032030125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" je"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032031195","data":{"timestamp":" 947032031194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" je"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032033770","data":{"timestamp":" 947032033770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JI"," userResponse":" JI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032034844","data":{"timestamp":" 947032034843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JI"," userResponse":" JI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032038899","data":{"timestamp":" 947032038898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JO"," userResponse":" JO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032039963","data":{"timestamp":" 947032039962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JO"," userResponse":" JO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032042606","data":{"timestamp":" 947032042605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ju"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JU"," userResponse":" JU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032043673","data":{"timestamp":" 947032043672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ju"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JU"," userResponse":" JU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032046816","data":{"timestamp":" 947032046814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ju"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032046912","data":{"timestamp":" 947032046912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" 8f0050e4-4358-458b-9520-ede6126d85b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ju"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JU"," userResponse":" JU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032063133","data":{"timestamp":" 947032063133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" dbe808c7-48bb-4bab-a804-31d19f9cda27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032067690","data":{"timestamp":" 947032067690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" dbe808c7-48bb-4bab-a804-31d19f9cda27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032072347","data":{"timestamp":" 947032072347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" dbe808c7-48bb-4bab-a804-31d19f9cda27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032076928","data":{"timestamp":" 947032076927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" dbe808c7-48bb-4bab-a804-31d19f9cda27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032081363","data":{"timestamp":" 947032081363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" dbe808c7-48bb-4bab-a804-31d19f9cda27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032086072","data":{"timestamp":" 947032086071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" dbe808c7-48bb-4bab-a804-31d19f9cda27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032090823","data":{"timestamp":" 947032090823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" dbe808c7-48bb-4bab-a804-31d19f9cda27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032095994","data":{"timestamp":" 947032095993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" dbe808c7-48bb-4bab-a804-31d19f9cda27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032100457","data":{"timestamp":" 947032100456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" dbe808c7-48bb-4bab-a804-31d19f9cda27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032104771","data":{"timestamp":" 947032104771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" dbe808c7-48bb-4bab-a804-31d19f9cda27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032110556","data":{"timestamp":" 947032110555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" dbe808c7-48bb-4bab-a804-31d19f9cda27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032124575","data":{"timestamp":" 947032124575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032124971","data":{"timestamp":" 947032124970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032125215","data":{"timestamp":" 947032125214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032125548","data":{"timestamp":" 947032125547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032125797","data":{"timestamp":" 947032125797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032129287","data":{"timestamp":" 947032129286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032129589","data":{"timestamp":" 947032129588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032130522","data":{"timestamp":" 947032130522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032130957","data":{"timestamp":" 947032130956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032133927","data":{"timestamp":" 947032133927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032134217","data":{"timestamp":" 947032134217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032135070","data":{"timestamp":" 947032135070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032135750","data":{"timestamp":" 947032135749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032136503","data":{"timestamp":" 947032136501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032136841","data":{"timestamp":" 947032136841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032137129","data":{"timestamp":" 947032137128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032137456","data":{"timestamp":" 947032137456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032137733","data":{"timestamp":" 947032137733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032141431","data":{"timestamp":" 947032141430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032141829","data":{"timestamp":" 947032141828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032142072","data":{"timestamp":" 947032142072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032142392","data":{"timestamp":" 947032142392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032142637","data":{"timestamp":" 947032142637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032146128","data":{"timestamp":" 947032146127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032146438","data":{"timestamp":" 947032146437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032147357","data":{"timestamp":" 947032147356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032147792","data":{"timestamp":" 947032147792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032150742","data":{"timestamp":" 947032150742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032151034","data":{"timestamp":" 947032151034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032151883","data":{"timestamp":" 947032151883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032152556","data":{"timestamp":" 947032152556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032153309","data":{"timestamp":" 947032153308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032153647","data":{"timestamp":" 947032153647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032153940","data":{"timestamp":" 947032153939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032154267","data":{"timestamp":" 947032154266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032154546","data":{"timestamp":" 947032154544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032157926","data":{"timestamp":" 947032157925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947032158055","data":{"timestamp":" 947032158055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_031441"," gameId":" ffbb17bd-f47e-4e9c-aa38-7c1fa9436057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}